[♪ opening theme song playing]
[indistinct chatter]
Hmm.
Yeah, I'm feelin' lucky.
Uh.
Hmm.
[GAMBLER]
This can't be happening!
-[grumbles]
-[chuckles] Oh, but it can.
When a player has a skill issue.
It's not skill!
No one draws winners
one after another!
-[JOOHEON] Hey.
-[gasps]
If you're done here, get lost.
I was hoping to play a round
against these guys.
Bite me.
-[growls]
-[gambler gasps]
[gasps]
[scoffs] Today sucks.
Well, you're a new face.
So let's get better acquainted.
[chuckles]
Sit.
[♪ dramatic music playing]
[JOOHEON] Straight.
Four of a kind.
Three aces.
-Royal flush!
-[all gasp]
I can't lose.
No way this is real.
[JOOHEON] Hmm.
[smirks]
"The Lucky Coin Blessed
by the Goddess of Fortune."
It was tossed
into a wishing well
and eventually became a relic.
[gasps] What? How'd you know?
[JOOHEON]
With your winning streak?
Hard not to.
Thing is, it's just C-rank.
No match with the double S
Bankruptcy aura
you're enveloped in.
[chuckling]
[BODYGUARD]
And this is the right way?
Um, Miss Holton?
[JOOHEON]
Her control has really improved.
Now that everyone here
is being pumped
with bad luck
except Jaeha and me,
even an average hand I play
is bound to win.
Take it and hit the road.
[JOOHEON] I want more.
More? This is all you wagered.
Cheating should
have a penalty, though.
Each of you owes $1 million.
What? Penalty?
-Who died and made you the--
-[Jooheon grunts]
[all gasp]
Please.
You didn't think
you'd get off scot-free.
That's just stupid.
-[gasps]
-[JOOHEON] Generous as I am,
I'll accept forms of payment
other than cash.
Like the Xu Fu relic
that lures children.
That works.
Huh?
And then,
tell me exactly
what Kiera's doing here.
In full detail.
Oh, I get it.
Bastard.
You planned this from the start.
Well, you won't get
a single word out of--
[screaming, grunting]
-[screaming]
-Hey. Hey! Mary!
[all groaning]
[gasps]
Irene strikes again.
[Mary and colleagues screaming]
They're screaming.
Maybe you-- [gasps]
Miss Holton?
[grunting in pain]
I'll talk!
Make it stop, and I'll tell you!
[JOOHEON] She changed her tune.
This worked out beautifully.
Glad you came around.
Let's hear it.
Go north,
till you get to a forest.
It has a tomb!
I don't know where Kiera is,
but... [groans]
Xu Fu's relic is there.
-[door opens]
-[gasps]
Miss Holton's gone!
-She ran off!
-[both gasp]
[gasps]
[panting] No.
Where'd you go, Irene?
Answer me!
-[panting]
-Hmm?
Damn it. The risk took effect.
That has to be why.
I gave her too much to handle.
If something happened,
it's my fault!
[grunts]
[panting]
Running around blindly
won't get me anywhere.
Just breathe and focus.
Sense her relic's aura
and follow the trail.
[takes deep breath]
[grunts]
Found her.
Back that way.
She's close!
[panting]
[sighs]
We have our hotel rooms.
Why'd she come here?
Mm.
[chuckles] Uh.
Jooheon.
Is she...
Ah.
It's the real Jooheon.
How are you feeling? [grunts]
W-What are you doing?
[grunting]
[Irene chuckling]
[JOOHEON] This is...
the relic, right?
[gasping]
[gasps]
♪
[sighs]
[grumbles] No, duh!
That much is clear!
Tell me these things in advance,
you stupid feathered bastard!
[KIERA] A Holton private jet?
Yes. So he's either working
with one of the Holtons,
or secretly teamed up
with someone connected to them.
We have the jet's course.
They're en route to Ghana.
A Holton in Ghana?
[smirks] I think I know why.
[JOOHEON] Hmm.
[JOOHEON]
Only children are allowed in.
Which means
Xu Fu's relic really is here.
So, Kiera conquered the tomb,
but chose not to seal it.
Question is why?
Give me the weakest relic
you have on you.
Dude! Are you gonna do
what I think you are?
[smirks]
[flint relic groans]
That's not what I'm used for!
[Jaeha yelling]
Could we please
use a normal entrance for once?
I can't take
these explosive detours.
I need more lives!
Being with you
will cost 100 at least!
Uh. Mm.
Aha!
How 'bout that?
Got service and everything.
[JAEHA] Yeah. Good stuff.
-But look up.
-Hmm?
[both gasp]
Hmm.
♪
[JAEHA] It's a huge field,
but somehow underground?
With just kids working on it.
They seem
a little too dedicated.
That explosion
didn't even faze them.
It's like
they're in a hypnotic trance.
Something is definitely off.
Hmm.
A minotaur.
Well, well.
A legendary figure
with a human body
and a bull's head
related to tea leaves
can only mean one thing.
This tea field was made
by Shennong's relic.
[gasps] Shennong?
[JOOHEON] He was the inventor
of the first farming tools
and taught mankind agriculture.
He'd also sample plants
to see which were medicinal
and which were poisonous,
then neutralize
any toxins he ingested
by chewing on tea leaves.
What about the relic of Xu Fu?
It should be tucked away
somewhere close.
This tea field must've been here
when Kiera's team
came to excavate.
Closing the tomb
would destroy the field,
so she left it open in order
to farm the tea leaves.
Problem is,
only children are allowed entry.
But with Xu Fu's relic,
she could lure tons
of local kids inside
to be her diligent workers.
So, I say we make
this trip twice as worthwhile
and bag ourselves two relics.
No, Jooheon, wait!
-The kids look mad!
-Huh?
Uh?
[growls]
[growling]
[grunting]
[BODYGUARD] Get down!
[groans]
Rope of Heaven!
-Tie all these crazy kids up!
-[ROPE] Here I go! Woo!
Play time, play time!
Whoop diddly-dee!
Lots of playmates all for me!
[sighs] Made it.
-Huh?
-Everything good over there?
Yes. We're both fine.
[JOOHEON] Hmm.
Why hello, relic.
You're just oozing with aura.
I barely had to look for you.
Hmm. [grunts]
[panting]
[grunts]
-[smirks]
-[worm screaming]
Get off!
Get off me right this instant!
Weird. Think I hear a voice.
Oh. It's you.
[worm grunts]
How did you find me?
I'm tiny!
The second you lost your cool,
you gave yourself away.
[WORM] Curses.
What kind of human are you?
[smirks]
[scoffs]
[WORM] Well,
tricks only get you so far!
-[scoffs]
-Easy.
I come in peace, not to fight.
[worm gasps]
You do?
Absolutely.
Calm down,
and let's make a deal.
Everyone's got a weakness,
and I know what yours is.
It's money.
What's it cost to buy you?
Wait, I'm confused.
Are you really negotiating
with a relic?
This little guy's
an extortionist.
The same way that Xu Fu was.
Can't be stingy if you wanna
form a contract with it.
It sells out?
[WORM] Ooh!
You're a man
I can do business with.
But you're gonna lose
that cocky grin
when you hear my hefty price.
[JOOHEON] Here's two million.
[ALL] What? $2 million?
But that's overkill!
[WORM] Oho!
The feel of authentic money!
It's not enough
to suffice, though.
-[Jooheon grunts]
-[WORM] Oh!
[JOOHEON]
And here's another two mil.
All for you.
[worm laughs]
It's raining money!
With that, are you willing
to come work under me?
[WORM] Nope.
It's a start, but still
not enough. [chuckles]
My current owner's down payment
was considerably higher.
[JOOHEON] Jeez, Kiera.
How much did you spend
to make this worm bite?
I added my emergency reserve
and some expensive jewelry.
Even had to throw in my watch.
Then, Irene offered
a property too.
[Irene laughs] Here you go!
[WORM] Woo-hoo-hoo!
I like an owner
who doesn't hold back,
so the deal is done!
What can I do for you,
moneybags?
Ah! I thought
you didn't wanna hurt me!
What's with the jar?
It's insurance.
I'm getting
my money's worth outta you.
-Now let's get to work.
-[WORM] Huh?
[JOOHEON] Rehypnotize the kids,
then have them pack up
all the tea leaves and saplings.
- We're leaving.
-[WORM] What?
Shennong's relic won't be happy.
I'm not paying for back talk!
[WORM] Speaking of,
this job will cost you
another 70 grand.
You need even more money now?
[WORM] That initial fee
is just the down payment.
Every command you give
will cost extra.
I'm not gonna
give you another dime
until we're out of here,
so work!
[worm screaming]
I understand, Master!
Please stop shaking me!
[SHENNONG] You scoundrels!
You would dare plunder my crops
and abandon my field?
[JOOHEON]
Look who decided to show.
-Worm!
-[WORM] Huh?
[JOOHEON] You know
where the exit is.
Guide everyone out.
[WORM] You really will pay me?
I don't do freebies.
Either be a guide
or an earthworm shake.
It's your choice.
[WORM] I'm a fantastic guide.
I even know a shortcut.
Here. Go on ahead.
We can't just leave you behind!
I'm gonna nab Shennong's relic.
I'll follow you
as soon as it's mine.
[SHENNONG]
You intend to claim me?!
[laughs]
[grunts]
-[Shennong growling]
-[Jooheon grunting]
Damn weeds!
[Shennong laughs]
Struggle all you want,
but there's no escape for you!
Not after taking my servants!
I will drag you
into the deepest pits of hell!
[gasps]
[Shennong yells]
[JOOHEON] It's sure persistent.
[IRENE] Jooheon!
-[Shennong grunts]
-[Jooheon grunts]
[gasps]
[grunting]
[screams]
[Irene grunting]
[Irene, Jaeha gasp]
-Where'd he go?
-Oh, man!
[gasps]
The tremors are getting worse!
We're leaving!
-Right now!
-[both panting]
[Jooheon groaning]
Talk about cheap.
[SHENNONG] Ha!
Says the rat who ruined my field
with the cheapest of tricks!
You enticed the worm
into betraying me!
[JOOHEON] Disguised itself
as one of its tea bushes, huh?
Shennong was revered as a god,
so his relic is
probably god-grade.
Dominance might not be enough.
[SHENNONG] Ah.
You've put away your sword.
Giving up already?
You wish. I just got an idea.
[SHENNONG] And what,
pray tell, was this epiphany?
My escape.
Doesn't seem like
there's a way out of this hole.
But then I thought,
"Hey, what if an exit opens up
if the one who owns this tomb
was dead?"
[SHENNONG] What?
[JOOHEON] "The First Ember
of Homo Erectus."
A D-rank relic
I swiped from the CIA.
[SHENNONG] That's your escape?
Blowing the tomb to bits?
And why not?
Thanks to all
your offshoots here,
there's lots of firewood.
One spark,
and everything goes boom.
[SHENNONG] Fool!
You'll perish in the blast!
I doubt it.
See, I'm pretty hard to kill.
You're up, ember,
so give it all you've got!
[FLINT RELIC] Ow, ow, ow!
You're gonna break me!
[SHENNONG] Suicidal lunatic!
You think I'll simply stand by?
-[grunting]
-[Shennong screaming]
[JOOHEON] Set everything ablaze!
[Shennong, flint relic yelling]
-[children yelling]
-[Irene panting]
[JAEHA] Take cover!
The tomb is collapsing!
[yells]
[Irene, Jaeha coughing]
-Do you see him?
-Oh, no!
[IRENE] Jooheon.
[sobbing]
He didn't make it.
[sniffling]
[gasps]
[Jooheon chuckles]
Why the long faces?
[all gasp]
[Jooheon chuckles]
So many tears.
I miss someone's funeral?
Then, you're okay?
Boss, I thought you died!
It just collapsed on you!
Why do you think it collapsed?
'Cause it was just sealed
by yours truly.
[sniffling]
I swear.
[sighs]
Think my heart stopped
for a second.
Jaeha seemed really
choked up about it too.
'Course I was!
Wait, time out!
I was worried
'cause you're my employer!
It was from a pragmatic mindset!
I'd be out of a stable day job
if you just went
and bit the dust!
So you could say
the one I was most worried about
-was me!
-[JOOHEON] Good to know.
[JAEHA] Huh?
You're still very much employed.
And guess what?
You have two more relics
in need of restoration.
Hold up.
Is this the First Ember?
Then this?
Is Shennong's relic.
I gave it
the roasting it deserved.
-[relics groaning]
-[JOOHEON] And the flint relic,
well, it just happened to be
the perfect makeshift bomb.
They're more like charcoal
than relics.
[JOOHEON] So?
Fix them. Unless you're saying
that you can't.
[JAEHA] No! I can fix them up
just fine! I promise!
[chuckles, sighs]
Why was I relieved to see him?
[♪ playing whimsical melody]
[TREE] Ah. Simply wonderful.
That drink hit the spot.
Sheesh.
Of all the jobs, how did I get
reduced to being a gardener?
Actually, I'm more like
the tree's personal butler.
When will it end?
[cell phone buzzing]
Huh?
Hey, boss. What's up?
Been a while since you called.
I don't even know where you are.
New York? Right. For sure.
First thing tomorrow.
You got it.
-[chuckles]
-What'd the boss have to say?
[SEUNGWOO] Pack up, boys.
Looks like we're finally free.
[traffic bustling]
[JAEHA] Boss.
Earth to boss.
-Come. In. Boss!
-[gasps]
Are we there yet?
We're still stuck in traffic.
-[sighs]
-We'll get there soon enough.
No one at the house will
answer their phones, though,
and I don't know why.
Our chauffeur's silence
is one thing,
but not even George
is responding to texts
or calls right now.
[yawns]
I wouldn't sweat it much.
We're one traffic jam away.
Right?
So your parents
will be healed real s--
[cell phone buzzing]
Seungwoo?
-What?
-[Seungwoo whimpering]
Boss! We've got a problem!
We were heading
to the rendezvous
when some dudes
started tailing us!
You're being chased?
[SEUNGWOO]
I think they're after the tree!
[JOOHEON] Is it Kiera?
She has the means
to investigate me,
so it's possible.
We're changing
the rendezvous point.
Just lose those goons.
Better not let them catch you.
Or I'll make sure
you die a brutal death.
-[SEUNGWOO] What?
-[hangs up]
Sounds like
there might be a problem
with the colleagues
that we're supposed to meet.
[smirks] They'll be fine.
My guys are craftier
than you'd think.
Driver.
Could you pick up the pace?
[JAEHA] If the road
wasn't packed tighter
than a can of sardines.
It's not usually this backed up.
Just caught an unlucky break.
-[explosion]
-Uh?
-[gasps]
-Was that a car?
[both gasp]
Jooheon's people
have the healing relic,
so if something bad
happens to them,
we'll lose the healing relic
and the chance
to save my parents.
[both exclaiming]
[JAEHA] Irene, think nice,
soothing thoughts!
[siren wailing in distance]
[panting]
We managed to lose the goons
and secure the tree!
[♪ closing theme song playing]